
//  Array of objects

const quiz = [
 {
    question:'Which of the following is not considered a JavaScript operator?',
    options:['new','this',' delete','typeof'],
    answer: 1
   
 },
 {
    question:'Why so JavaScript and Java have similar name?',
    options:['JavaScript is a stripped-down version of Java',
    'JavaScript\'s syntax is loosely based on Java\'s',
    
    ' They both originated on the island of Java '
    ,'None of the above'],
    answer:  1
   
 },
 {
    question:'When a user views a page containing a JavaScript program, which machine actually executes the script?',
    options:['The User\'s machine running a Web browser',
    'The Web server',
   'A central machine deep within Netscape\'s corporate offices',
   'None of the above'
],
    answer: 0
 },
 {
    question:'Choose the client-side JavaScript object?',
    options:['Database',' Cursor','Client',
   'FileUpLoad'],
    answer: 3
 },
 {
    question:'______method evaluates a string of JavaScript code in the context of the specified object.',
    options:['Efloat',' ParseInt','Eval' , 'ParseFloat'],
    answer: 2
 }
,{
   question:'__________ JavaScript is also called server-side JavaScript.',
   options:['Microsoft','Navigator','LiveWire' , 'Native' ],
   answer: 2
}
,{
   question:' _____ JavaScript statements embedded in an HTML page can respond to user events such as mouse-clicks, form input, and page navigation.',
   options:['Client-side',' Server-side','Local','Native'],
   answer: 0

}
,{
   question:'What are variables used for in JavaScript Programs?',
   options:['Storing numbers, dates, or other values','Varying randomly','Causing high-school algebra flashbacks','None of the above'],
   answer: 0
}
,{
   question:'__________ JavaScript is also called client-side JavaScript.',
   options:['Microsoft','Navigator','LiveWire','Native'],
   answer: 1
}
,{
   question:'Which of the following are capabilities of functions in JavaScript?',
   options:['Return a value','Accept parameters and Return a value','Accept parameters','None of the above'],
   answer: 2
}
]
